{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "estimate",
      "answer": "估計",
    },
    {
      "question": "calculate",
      "answer": "計算",
    },
    {
      "question": "enumerate",
      "answer": "計數",
    },
    {
      "question": "variant",
      "answer": "變量",
    },
    {
      "question": "aggregate",
      "answer": "總合",
    },
    {
      "question": "cone",
      "answer": "圓錐",
    },
    {
      "question": "plumb",
      "answer": "垂直",
    },
    {
      "question": "geometry",
      "answer": "幾何學",
    },
    {
      "question": "dual",
      "answer": "雙重的",
    },
    {
      "question": "qualitative",
      "answer": "定性的",
    },
    {
      "question": "circuitous",
      "answer": "迂迴的",
    },
    {
      "question": "caliber",
      "answer": "才能",
    },
    {
      "question": "dispersion",
      "answer": "離差",
    },
    {
      "question": "cohesive",
      "answer": "黏著的",
    },
    {
      "question": "bulk",
      "answer": "大部分",
    },
    {
      "question": "brim",
      "answer": "邊緣",
    },
    {
      "question": "rim",
      "answer": "邊框",
    },
    {
      "question": "constituent",
      "answer": "要素",
    },
    {
      "question": "impetus",
      "answer": "推動力",
    },
    {
      "question": "decelerate",
      "answer": "減速",
    },
    {
      "question": "precipitate",
      "answer": "加速降落",
    },
    {
      "question": "expedite",
      "answer": "暢通",
    },
    {
      "question": "quiver",
      "answer": "震動",
    },
    {
      "question": "diffuse",
      "answer": "散布的",
    }
  ]
}
